And if you can do more with Sonnet 5.5 with one or two point out of Opus, which is already
save you a shit ton of money compared to Fable.
Yeah, that's perfect.
Yeah, exactly.
The big, big one was Claude Opus 5.5, which took the timeline big time because, yeah,
27 million views.
Yeah.
They somehow do good on marketing.
Yeah because people are happy right?
Yeah.
FiveFive better than Fable 5.1 and what's happening I expect them to have Fable 5.5
and they and Fable 5.5 or whatever the next version is getting distilled into Opus and
from yesterday Sonnet and those models are really good.
Yeah because at this moment why would you even want to use Fable?
One of the things it's too expensive for the output that you have, and you have more or
less the same output with today, obvious.
I just closed all of my favor session.
Yeah.
Bye bye.
Dented coding 50% to 66, 10% more, mutual personal reasoning.
Okay.
Two point more.
Business workflow 40%.
It's fucking nuts.
user, I still prefer the OpenAI computer used in codecs. I think it's better. The Claude
one is a bit annoying. College Walk 1846. Mentor. Yesterday, because we are always good
on timing, Sonnet 5.5.
Yes. And you tried it.
Yes, the whole morning.
I, um, I was on my Clodes weekly subscription, um, 24%.
I work the whole morning and I'm still running on Fume right now.
I have 1%, but, uh, it's still going.
I love Soné.
I think I will run an audit of all of the pull requests with Clodes.
I need to see if it's using more tokens and more usage that to have the verifier as a
smarter model than Sonnet.
But basically, xi high, no, this one is xi.
Looks like the both high, opus 5 have the same result.
So any cheaper, so that's a better choice.
Input token two instead of four and output 10 instead of 20.
Yeah.
So that's a big discount.
And yeah, the pricing is cheaper.
So we like that.
So we can spend more tasks.
Working with Opus feel a bit not unlimited, but at least we have a usage.
I go from 36 hours to 72.
Yeah, well, I never go through my usage.
So I'm happy.
And yeah, okay, so way above 5.5, cheaper and perform at the same level than the Astra.
So let's go.
But I had the same issue on Grok bot. That's running on 4.7 now as well, right?
Yeah.
Because I gave it like tasks, and then I have my manager that just does managing, and it
talks to all the bots that have that task. And then after a while, when a bot doesn't
its task instead of reminding him and checking the the prompts on that it should do it the
manager just decides hey he isn't doing it so from now on I am going to do it.
Yeah so your manager is implementing instead of managing?
Yeah so I think you can run something that is been defined by Opus on a PRD
implement it with Sonnet and have a verifier after that. That would make sense I think.
That's what I'm going to experiment this week and see how it goes and...
Yeah I just thought that Opus if it does sub agents it would use Sonnet as always.
So yeah you have your orchestrator in Opus and then you can put all of the Sonnet guys,
a Sonnet agent behind it.
And I dropped that and said, okay, no,
do not use Fable 5 anymore.
Use Sonnet as the default model
and Opus for scheduling and orchestration.
Okay, yeah, this one I like a lot.
Ask Opus 5 for a video of data center.
The result is beyond what I could imagine.
And the thing is,
Where is my tweet?
I told Claude to browse the internet and find whatever he wanted to use.
So it didn't generate the video, it just went on internet and put them all together.
Our civilization was built on technology.
It is the glory of human ambition and achievement.
And we have invented a new technology.
Nice, right.
You can see that on Netflix.
it took video from the internet and put them together. Let's go.
Yeah, it's getting really smart.
Yeah. And even the timing and stuff, everything is lit.
By the end, it forgot the beginning. But one small word refused to fade. Then, in the summer
of 2017. Every word saw every other word, not one after another, all at once.
And yeah. Before you would need a team to just create something like that.
In a week, two hours, one prompt, Claude quietly built something so-called the Crater of the Gate.
I gave my opus 5.55 one of the French theory analysis that got 80 million views and simply
us to donate it to a video and then yeah garbage of our time the author is dead and the reader reigns
Deleuze taught us to prefer the rhizome to the tree the nomad to the settler desire to law
becoming to being like you can see it's always the same animation the same style but others
It's the same as websites, right? Everybody who has the website built fully by Claude,
you just recognize it. Yeah. But it works nice.
I don't mind. It looks good. It does what it needs to do. So yeah. Otherwise, just spend a few hours
more doing the details and asking it to change it. Exactly. One guy spent 15 minutes on a video.
If you want to make it perfect, spend the next three hours and then you will have
something even better, right?
Yeah.
And it's still pretty fast.
And also, last topic, um, did you read this article or drop it into your agent?
Uh, getting the most out of Opus 5.5 in Claude and CloudGuard, uh, how to ask
so much guidelines to what's new and, uh, what you should do, how you should talk
to it, so say what's done look like and let it run so you have a stop and you
have proof of what Opus is going to search for, for example, take a
screenshot, send me a screenshot of the videos, let me verify it.
A clear stop.
It's even better.
It's a requirement, right?
And you can ask for proof of it.
So my good payment, head point from the whole client to the new one, that means
every endpoint use the new client, the whole client is deleted and the test should
passes stop as a, and ask me only if there is a test file for a reason.
You can't explain.
Okay.
So you can use like, um, negatives.
So when you, when you prompt an image or a video steering along,
uh, code God, tell me where it tell it, which, uh, stop you want.
Yeah.
So it's by the same, same stuff.
You dropped that.
Do you tell Claude to, um, rewrite your Claude MD and agent MD?
And that was great.
Yeah.
and see like, okay, so Max, what is it?
- Max is lower than x high.
- Yes, because, okay, so Sonnet scores lower at max effort
than x high, for which our code evaluated
whether a code change could be merged with short human edits
it penalize out of scopes change even if they are high
quality or helpful.
At max effort, Sonnet F5 more often run code review skills.
Okay. Because an effort allow you to increase the amount of, uh, efforts slash rounds that
you want to put in a task. So that's why that's the time. Okay. So for example,
the time to think between for the same prompt. So one minute on low, medium, four minutes high,
11 minutes and max one hour. Yeah. But it's not that crazy.
I don't like the max one.
I was going to say I like one of the first two.
Yeah, exactly. Medium looks better.
My goal was to iterate and give feedback.
Low effort would get there much faster.
But max effort gave me something much more polished right off the bat.
Run the apps, you find a bug, you drop it, it fixes it right away.
And it worked great with Grok 4.52 because it was fast as fuck.
Yes.
And you can pile up the prompt.
You test the app, you throw all of the bugs, it's fixing it for chip.
You check it again.
And while you are checking it and like testing something else in the
app, it just like, "code, code, code."
And then you come back to it and then boom.
That was sick.
So far, which one is best one for you?
So, right now I can say last night I'm using Sonnet.
I was using Sonnet until my subscription run out.
I want to try it until next week.
Well, I can tell you if it was a mistake or not.
I will build with a Sonnet 5.5 and check it maybe at the end of the
day or every few hours inside.
All of the pull requests, I will check them with Opus.
If you can do more with Sonnet 5.5 with one or two points out of
Opus, which is already save you a shit ton of money compared to Fable.
Yeah, that's perfect.
Yeah, exactly.
using Opus because I didn't try Sonnet yet, but I'm in the middle of a project, so I don't want
to switch. I'm always afraid that everything will break and I have to explain everything again.
I'm pretty sure Opus will use Sonnet in the background anyway, you just don't
going to notice it. So yeah, you will use Sonnet one way or another with the agent.
Yeah. Just hope that they use the cheaper token usage as well. And don't just say,
hey you're using Opus. - Michel, thank you so much for your time and that was nice getting back online
next week, same time, same place. - Yes, same time, same place. - Let's go, thank you so much everyone, thank
you for joining us and like, subscribe, share the video and we will see you next week. - Yes, bye.